Guide to the Islamic Fundamentalist Audio Recordings Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Tape 654. A sermon on the sacred mosque, Circa 1990-2000; 1 (Box 654)
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ?????? ?????? ?? ??? ????? ???? ?? ?????? ?? ?? ?????? ?????. ???? ??????? ???? ?? ?????? ?????? ??????? ?????? ?? ????? ???? ????? ?????? ?? ??? ????? ???????. ???? ??????? ?? ???? ???? ? ???? ?????? ??????? ?????????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ?? ???? ????????? ???? ???????? ??????? ??????. ????? ??????? ???? ???? ???? ???????? ??? ?????? ???????? ????? ??? ?????? ???. ?? 35:53 ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ???? ??????? ????? 1 ??? 7 ? ?????? ????? 1 ??? 23
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 655. Sermons about power of God and the death of the prophet Muh?ammad, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 655)
  Comments: The recording on side A starts with a speaker who talks Farsi language. Side A 45:44 min. Side B 45:39 min.
  Side A: A recording of part of a sermon about the power of God in which a speaker recites verses from the Qur?a?n and tells stories about the creation of Heavens and Earth. From 37:59 a recording of a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura al-H?ijr 1-66.
  Side B: The same speaker gives a sermon about the death of the prophet Muh?ammad in which he addresses the Prophet's illness, last pilgrimage, and the last moments of his life. From 46:10 a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura al-Ma??idah 1-8.
  ?????????: ???? ??????? ?? ????? ????? ?????? ????? ????? ????????. ??? ????? ????? 45:44 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 45:39 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?? ???? ?? ???? ??????. ???? ??????? ???? ?? ?????? ?????? ?? ????? ??? ???????? ? ?????. ?? 37:59 ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?? ???? ????? ????? 1 ??? 66
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ???? ?????? ???? ???? ???? ??? ????, ??? ??????, ? ??????? ??????? ?? ?????. ?? 40:16 ????? ?? ?????? ????? ??????? ????? 1 ??? 8
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 656. A sermon on patience, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 656)
  Comments: Side A 29:53 min. Side B 30:00 min.
  Side A: A speaker gives a sermon in which he recites and interprets verses from the Qur?a?n and talks about the patience of the Prophet in hard times and the event of calamities.
  Side B: The same speaker tells stories about committing sins and repentance. The speaker advises the audience to persevere reading the Qur?a?n and praying. From 27:06 a recording of a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura al-Isra?? 79-88.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 29:53 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 30:00 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ???? ???? ???? ?? ?????? ? ?????? ?????? ? ????? ?? ??? ? ??? ??? ?????? ???? ????? ?? ??????? ??????? ? ?????? ??????? ? ??? ???? ???????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ????? ?? ?????, ?????? ?????? ? ??????. ???? ??????? ????????? ??? ????? ?????? ? ??????. ?? 27:06 ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ????? ??????? ????? 79 ??? 88
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 657. The interpretation of Sura al-Baqarah, Circa 1987-2000; 1 (Box 657)
  Comments: Side A 46:34 min. Side B 45:41 min.
  Side A: A speaker recites and interprets verses from Sura al-Baqarah to the audience.
  Side B: The same speaker continues the interpretation of verses from Sura al-Baqarah. From 23:17 a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura al-Nisa?? 1-57.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 46:34 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 45:41 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ???? ?????? ? ?????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ??????? ????? ?? ???? ??????. ?? 23:17 ????? ?? ?????? ????? ?????? ????? 1 ??? 57
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 658. A sermon on faith, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 658)
  Comments: Side A 29:42 min. Side B 29:00 min.
  Side A: A speaker gives a sermon in which he recites and interprets verses from the Qur?a?n about faith. The speaker tells stories from the history of Islam about a number of Muslim military commanders such as Qutaybah ibn Muslim al-Ba?hili? and about the conquests of Persia and Afghanistan.
  Side B: The same speaker urges for adhering to the obligations and teachings of Islam. The speaker answers questions from the audience about different issues such as Jihad and commitment to religious obligations. From 25:53 a recording of a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura al-T?u?r 1-34.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 29:42 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 29:00 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ??????? ? ?????? ???? ????? ?? ?????? ?? ??????? ??????? ??????. ???? ??????? ????? ?? ??????? ???????? ?? ??? ?????? ????????? ???????? ??? ????? ?? ???? ??????? ? ?? ??? ???? ???? ? ?????????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ??? ??????? ???????? ? ???????? ???????? ? ??????. ???? ??????? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?????? ???? ?????? ? ???????? ??????? ???????. ?? 25:53 ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ????? ????? ????? 1 ??? 34
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 659. The interpretation of Sura al-Anbiya??, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 659)
  Comments: Side A 47:25 min. Side B 47:43 min. Speaker: one of the speakers is Muh?ammad ibn S?a?lih? al-?Uthaymi?n.
  Side A: A speaker recites and interprets verses from the Qur?a?n of Sura al-Anbiya??.
  Side B: The speaker tells the story of the killing of ?Abd Alla?h ibn al-Zubayr and Hadiths about menstruation and ablution. From 32:43 a recording of part of lecture about the virtues of the Qur?a?n in which a speaker interprets pertinent Hadiths from S?ah?i?h? al-Bukha?ri?.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 47:25 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 47:43 ?????. ???????: ??? ????????? ?? ???? ?? ???? ????????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ???? ???????? ? ?????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ??? ???? ??? ???? ?? ??????. ???? ??????? ?????? ????? ?? ????? ? ??????. ?? 32:43 ????? ????? ?? ?????? ?? ????? ?????? ???? ???? ??????? ?????? ????? ????? ???? ??????? ?? ???? ???????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 660. A session on S?ah?i?h? al-Bukha?ri?, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 660)
  Comments: Side B is actually the beginning and it continues on side A. Side A 48:14 min. Side B 48:10 min. Speaker: ?A??id? al-Qurani?.
  Side A: The same speaker reads and interprets a number of Hadiths from S?ah?i?h? al-Bukha?ri?.
  Side B: A recording of a session in which the speaker reads and interprets a number of S?ah?i?h? al-Bukha?ri?.
  ?????????: ?????? ??????. ??? ????? ????? 48:14 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 48:10 ?????. ???????: ???? ??????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ??? ???????? ??????? ?? ???? ??????? ? ?????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ????? ???? ?? ???? ??????? ???? ??? ??????? ??? ???????? ??????? ?? ???? ??????? ? ?????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 661. Multiple topics, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 661)
  Comments: Side A 28:45 min. Side B 30:38 min. Speaker: one of the speakers is ?A??id? al-Qurani?.
  Side A: A recording of a poetry reading and a congregational prayer. From 10:06 a recitation from the Qur?a?n from verse 1 of Sura al-Muja?dalah to verse 5 of Sura al-Mumtah?ina.
  Side B: A recording of a speaker who answers questions about different issues such as hypocrisy and the life of women in heaven.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 28:45 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 30:38 ?????. ???????: ??? ????????? ?? ???? ??????
  ????? ?????: ????? ?????? ????? ????? ? ???? ?????. ?? 10:06 ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?? ????? 1 ?? ???? ???????? ??? ????? 5 ?? ???? ????????
  ????? ??????: ????? ?????? ???? ?? ????? ?? ?????? ?????? ???? ?????? ? ???? ?????? ?? ?????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 662. A sermon on ibn ?Umar, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 662)
  Comments: Side A 30:46 min. Side B 30:33 min.
  Side A: A speaker gives a sermon in which he talks about the biography of ?Umar ibn al-Khat?t?a?b and reads and interprets Hadiths which were narrated by ibn ?Umar.
  Side B: The same speaker talks about the biography of ibn ?Umar and reads and interprets Hadiths which were narrated by ibn ?Umar.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 30:46 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 30:33 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ????? ???? ?? ???? ??? ??? ?? ??????. ???? ??????? ??? ???????? ??????? ??????? ?? ??? ??? ? ?????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ?? ???? ??? ???. ???? ??????? ??? ???????? ??????? ??????? ?? ??? ??? ? ?????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 663. A sermon about singing, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 663)
  [Duplicate of Tape 646].
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 664. A sermon about loving God, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 664)
  Comments: Side B is actually the beginning and it continues on side A. Side A 46:05 min. Side B 45:10 min.
  Side A: The same speaker tells stories and reads Hadiths about Sa?d ibn Abi? Waqqa?s?. From 34:45 a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura A?l ?Umra?n1-62.
  Side B: A speaker gives a sermon in which he talks about the key to the love of God. The speaker recites and interprets pertinent verses from the Qur?a?n and Hadiths.
  ?????????: ?????? ??????. ??? ????? ????? 46:05 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 45:10 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ????? ? ?????? ????? ?? ??? ?? ??? ????. ?? 34:45 ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ????? ?? ????? ????? 1 ??? 62
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ???? ????? ???? ?? ?????? ??? ???? ????. ???? ??????? ???? ?? ?????? ? ?????? ????? ?? ??? ??????? ? ?????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 665. A lecture about death, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 665)
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 666. A sermon on the prophet Muh?ammad, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 666)
  Comments: Side B is actually the beginning and it continues on side A. Side A 45:35 min. Side B 45:15 min.
  Side A: The same speaker talks about a number of Islamic scholars such as al-Sha?fi?i? and urges preachers to follow his example.
  Side B: A speaker gives a sermon on the prophet Muh?ammad in which he addresses the prophet's character as a messenger of God and a leader of a nation.
  ?????????: ?????? ??????. ??? ????? ????? 45:35 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 45:15 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ??????? ?? ??? ????? ???????? ??? ??????? ? ???? ?????? ???????? ???
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ?????? ???? ?????? ???? ?????? ????? ? ???? ???
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 667. A sermon about commitment to religious duties, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 667)
  Comments: Side A 24:20 min. Side B 23:37 min.
  Side A: A speaker gives a sermon about commitment to religious duties, committing sins, and repentance. The speaker tells stories from the history of Islam about committing sins and repentance.
  Side B: The same speaker emphasizes on commitment to religious duties and the teachings of Islam. From 4:19 another speaker chants religious anthems and prayers.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 24:20 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 23:37 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ???????? ??????? ??????? ? ?????? ??????? ? ??????.???? ??????? ????? ?? ??????? ???????? ?? ?????? ??????? ? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ??? ???????? ??????? ??????? ? ?????? ????? ????????. ?? 4:19 ????? ?????? ???? ?????? ????? ? ?????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 668. A sermon about Andalusia, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 668)
  Comments: Side A 44:23 min. Side B 43:27 min.
  Side A: A speaker gives a sermon about Andalusia in which he talks about the fall of states and nations and cites and interprets pertinent Hadiths.
  Side B: The same speaker states that there is a presence of ethical corruption due to deviation from the teachings of Islam in many Muslim countries. The speaker believes that enemies of Islam have exploited this to divide Muslims.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 44:23 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 43:27 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ??????? ????? ???? ?? ?????? ????? ? ????? ? ?????? ??????? ????? ?? ??? ??????? ? ?????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ????? ?????? ?? ??????? ???? ?????? ?? ???????? ??????? ????? ???????? ?? ?????? ?? ????? ????????? ?????? ??? ????? ??????? ??????? ??? ?????? ????????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 669. A lecture about ibn Ba?z, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 669)
  Comments: Side A 46:49 min. Side B 46:46 min.
  Side A: A speaker gives a lecture about ?Abd al-?Azi?z ibn Ba?z in which he addresses his biography, knowledge, and jobs which he occupied in Saudi Arabia.
  Side B: The same speaker talks about the stance of ?Abd al-?Azi?z ibn Ba?z in the issue of executing Sayyid Qut?b. The speaker reads to the audience some of ibn Ba?z's views and advisory opinions. From 31:18 a recording of part of a sermon about the role of preachers in reviving and proselytizing the Islamic religion and its teachings. The recording cuts off at the end of side B.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 46:49 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 46:46 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ?????? ?? ??? ?????? ?? ??? ????? ???? ?? ????? ???????, ????, ? ??????? ???? ?????? ? ??????? ???? ????? ?? ????????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ?? ???? ??? ?????? ?? ??? ?? ????? ??? ???. ???? ??????? ?????? ??? ???? ? ????? ??? ?????? ?? ???. ?? 31:18 ????? ????? ?? ???? ?? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ????? ???????? ? ??? ??????? ? ????? ????? ???. ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 670. A sermon about affliction, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 670)
  Comments: Side A 44:15 min. Side B 44:06 min.
  Side A: A speaker talks about the affliction of human beings and believes it is a trial from God to the man's patience and faith.
  Side B: The same speaker recites and interprets verses from the Qur?a?n about patience and resorting to God in calamities. From 23:01 a recording of a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura al-Nu?r 11-58.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 44:15 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 44:06 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ??????? ?? ?????? ??????? ?????? ??? ??? ?????? ?? ???? ??????? ??? ??????? ? ????? ???? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ?????? ??????? ?????? ?? ????? ? ????????? ????? ?? ????. ?? 23:01 ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ????? ????? ????? 11 ??? 58
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 671. A sermon about the prophets Ibra?hi?m and Mu?sa?, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 671)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. Side A 47:47 min. Side B 45:52 min.
  Side A: A speaker gives a sermon about the prophet Ibra?hi?m and recites and interprets verses from the Qur?a?n about his journey to Makkah and building of Ka?bah.
  Side B: The same speaker gives a sermon about the prophet Mu?sa? and recites and interprets verses from the Qur?a?n about his story with the Pharaoh of Egypt.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 47:47 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 45:52 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ????? ??????? ? ???? ???? ?? ?????? ? ?????? ?????? ?? ??? ????? ??? ??? ? ????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ????? ???? ? ???? ???? ?? ?????? ? ?????? ?????? ?? ???? ?? ????? ???
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 672. A sermon about al-Sunnah wa-al-Jama??ah, 1992; 1 (Box 672)
  Comments: Side A 29:06 min. Side B 28:21 min. Speaker: ?A??id? al-Qurani?.
  Side A: A speaker gives a sermon in which he talks about the attributes of al-Sunnah wa-al-Jama??ah and tells stories from the history of Islam about ?Umar ibn al-Khat?t?a?b and some of the Prophet's companions.
  Side B: The same speaker answers questions about different issues such as Jihad in Afghanistan, the human genetic traits, and some jurisprudential issues.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 29:06 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 28:21 ?????. ???????: ???? ??????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ????? ???? ?? ???? ??? ????? ? ??????? ????? ????? ?? ??????? ???????? ?? ??? ?? ?????? ? ??? ????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ?? ????? ?? ?????? ?????? ???? ?????? ?? ?????????, ?????? ???????? ?? ???????, ? ??? ??????? ???????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 673. Sermons about hypocrites and Afghani Mujahideen, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 673)
  Comments: Side A 23:57 min. Side B 24:06 min.
  Side A: A speaker gives a sermon in which he addresses the attributes of hypocrites and explains their attempts in devastation of Islam during various stages in the history of Islam.
  Side B: The same speaker gives a sermon in which he delivers a gratitude letter to Afghani Mujahideen and praises their role in Jihad in Afghanistan.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 23:57 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 24:06 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ????????? ?????? ???? ?????? ? ????????? ?????? ??????? ???? ????? ?????? ?? ??????? ????????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ????????? ??????? ???? ???? ????? ??? ?????? ? ?????? ????? ???? ????? ?? ?????? ?? ?????????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 674. Sermons about the miracles of prophets and stories from the history of Islam, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 674)
  Comments: Side A 46:07 min. Side B 44:07 min.
  Side A: A speaker gives a sermon about the miracles of prophets in which he particularly talks about the Qur?a?n as the miracle of the prophet Muh?ammad. The speaker recites and interprets verses from the Qur?a?n about inimitability of the eloquence in the Qur?a?n.
  Side B: A recording of another speaker who tells stories from the history of Islam and cites and interprets verses from the Qur?a?n and Hadiths about adultery and its punishment and obedience to parents.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 46:07 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 44:07 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ?????? ??? ???????? ??????? ????? ?????? ???? ????? ?? ??????. ???? ??????? ???? ?? ?????? ?? ??????? ?? ????? ?????? ? ?????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ????? ?????? ??? ???? ????? ?? ??????? ???????? ?? ????? ? ?????? ? ???? ????????? ? ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ? ?????? ????? ?? ??? ??????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 675. A sermon about the Prophet's companions, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 675)
  Comments: Side B is actually the beginning and it continues on side A. Side A 44:15 min. Side B 44:40 min.
  Side A: The same speaker tells stories and talks about the biographies of ?Uthma?n ibn ?Affa?n and ?Ali? ibn Abi? T?a?lib and their support to the Prophet. From 38:50 a recording of a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura Ya?si?n 1-30.
  Side B: A speaker gives a sermon about the Prophet's companions in which he tells stories and talks about the biographies of Abu? Bakr al-S?iddi?q and ?Umar ibn al-Khat?t?a?b and their support to the Prophet.
  ?????????: ?????? ??????. ??? ????? ????? 44:15 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 44:40 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ??????? ?? ???? ????? ?? ???? ? ??? ?? ??? ???? ? ???????? ?????? ????? ????? ?? ???. ?? 38:50 ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ????? ?? ????? 1 ??? 30
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ???? ?? ????? ?????? ????? ???? ?? ???? ??? ??? ?????? ? ??? ?? ?????? ? ??????? ?? ?????? ? ???? ????? ?? ???
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 676. A lecture about death, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 676)
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 677. Multiple topics, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 677)
  Comments: Side A 29:59 min. Side B 28:57 min. Speaker: ?A??id? al-Qurani?.
  Side A: A recording of Q&A session in which the speaker answers questions about different jurisprudential issues such as fasting, good deeds, the life of women paradise. The speaker cites and interprets to the audience pertinent verses from the Qur?a?n and Hadiths.
  Side B: The same speaker reads a poem in which he praises the Afghani Mujahideen. From 4:44 a recording of a congregational prayer. From 10:08 a recording of a recitation from the Qur?a?n from verse 1 of Sura al-Muja?dalah to verse 5 of Sura al-Mumtah?ina.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ?????29:59 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 28:57 ?????. ???????: ???? ??????
  ????? ?????: ????? ?????? ? ????? ???? ???? ??????? ?? ????? ????? ?????? ??? ??????, ????? ??????, ? ???? ?????? ?? ????? ?????? ? ?????? ????? ?? ?????? ? ?????? ????? ? ?????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ????? ????? ???? ????????? ???????. ?? 4:44 ????? ????? ?????. ?? 10:08 ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?? ????? 1 ?? ???? ???????? ??? ????? 5 ?? ???? ????????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 678. A sermon on patience, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 678)
  [Duplicate of Tape 656].
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 679. A lecture about death, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 679)
  [Duplicate of Tape 665].
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 680. Stories from the history of Islam, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 680)
  Comments: Side A 21:46 min. Side B 21:42 min.
  Side A: A recording of a speaker who tells many stories from the Qur?a?n and the history of Islam about faith, patience, and good deeds.
  Side B: The same speaker tells more stories about faith, patience, and good deeds.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 21:46 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 21:42 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ?????? ???? ??? ??? ?? ??????? ???????? ??? ?????? ?? ???????, ?????, ? ????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ?????? ?? ????? ?? ???????, ?????, ?????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 681. A sermon about righteous deeds and falsehood and the cultural invasion, Circa 1990-2000; 1 (Box 681)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. Side A 45:22 min. Side B 45:05 min.
  Side A: A recording of a sermon in which he talks about righteous deeds and falsehood and tells stories about the conflict between the Pharaoh of Egypt with the prophet Mu?sa? and the conflict between the non believers and the Prophet Muh?ammad.
  Side B: The same speaker talks about cultural invasion methods against Islam. The speaker answers questions on different issues such as the methodology of al-Ba?th party, the influence of media in the cultural invasion, the ruling party in Sudan, Saddam Hussein and the invasion of Kuwait.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 45:22 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 45:05 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ????? ???? ??????? ?? ?????? ??? ???? ? ?????? ????? ????? ?? ????? ??? ? ????? ?? ????? ???? ??? ????? ???? ? ????? ?? ?????? ????? ??? ???
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ?? ????? ????? ?????? ?????? ?? ???????. ???? ??????? ?? ????? ?? ?????? ?????? ???? ???? ??? ?????, ????? ??????? ?? ????? ??????, ? ????? ?????? ?? ???????, ? ???? ???? ? ????? ??????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 682. A lecture about death, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 682)
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 683. A sermon about singing, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 683)
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 684. A sermon about dialogue, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 684)
  Comments: Side A 29:39 min. Side B 29:30 min.
  Side A: A recording of a sermon in which a speaker tells stories and talks about the rules and ethics of dialogue in the Islamic perspective.
  Side B: The speaker answers questions from the audience about different jurisprudential issues. From 7:35 a recording of a congregational prayer.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 29:39 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 29:30 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ????? ???? ??????? ?? ????? ? ???? ?????? ????? ??????? ????????. ???? ??????? ????? ?? ??? ??? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ?? ????? ?? ?????? ????? ??????. ?? 7:35 ????? ????? ?????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 685. A sermon on faith, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 685)
  Comments: Side A 24:35 min. Side B 24:33 min.
  Side A: A speaker gives a sermon in which he recites and interprets verses from the Qur?a?n and reviews some of the opinions of Salafi?yah scholars about believing and sincerity in worship to God.
  Side B: The speaker answers questions from the audience about different issues such as media and veil. From 18:52 a recording of part of a sermon on faith in which a speaker recites and interprets pertinent verses from the Qur?a?n to the audience.